### Cillian Molloy

## **Contact Details (including Town and County)**

Phone: 045 521123 Mobile: +353 85 2721551

Email: Cillian.molloy@yahoo.ie Linkedin: linkedin.com/cillianmolloy

#### **PROFILE**

I am a graduate of the Institute of Technology Tallaght, Dublin with an Honours Degree in Computing Science. I have made several small software applications during my time in College that were for personal learning and experience. I am open to criticism, and I can use the feedback to improve my role in the organization and in future projects.

#### **CAREER HISTORY**

## Car Park Security, Irish National Stud and Gardens Current

15/6/2015 -

- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc.
- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use Cillian Molloy

Contact Details (including Town and County)

Phone: 045 521123 Mobile: +353 85 2721551

Email: Cillian.molloy@yahoo.ie Linkedin: linkedin.com/cillianmolloy

#### **PROFILE**

I am a graduate of the Institute of Technology Tallaght, Dublin with an Honours Degree in Computing Science. I have made several small software applications during my time in College that were for personal learning and experience. I am open to criticism, and I can use the feedback to improve my role in the organization and in future projects.

#### **CAREER HISTORY**

Car Park Security, Irish National Stud and Gardens 15/6/2015 - Current

- · Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc.
- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc..
- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc...

Customer Attendant, Tesco 28/11/2012 – 15/12/2013

- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc..
- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc..

#### Achievements:

During my time working in the Irish National Stud in 2017, on days with many incoming customers, I had to direct cars to the three parking areas with no staff or security to aid me. Through careful placement of vehicles and knowledge of how much space was available, I was able to ensure that customers would be able to park and enter the tourist grounds. I was later informed that through my actions, I had helped the stud make a turnover larger than the season of 2016.

EDUCATION & TRAINING
RESULTS PENDING
University name TBC/5/2018

Games and Apps Designer
Carlow PLC 12/11/2013

Graduated

Rathangan High School 12/12/2009

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS None

## IT SKILLS & LANGUAGES

- Include details of all IT skills and software knowledge you have to offer potential employers. Example: IT Skills: Wordpress, AutoCad, Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook and Explorer.
- List languages and competency level conversational, fluent, mother tongue etc.

#### **INTERESTS**

I have interests in sculpting and modelling, having handmade miniatures using modelling clay and soft wax, and animation and the technical aspects behind it, such as rendering, resource management and movement.

I would like to combine my modelling hobby with 3D printing and scanning technology to put my creations into a 3D rendering and sculpting software tool to refine the detail on them.

active verbs including sold, solved etc..

Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc..

#### **Customer Attendant, Tesco**

28/11/2012 - 15/12/2013

- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc..
- Insert further details of your key duties and responsibilities. Remember to use active verbs including sold, solved etc..

#### **Achievements:**

During my time working in the Irish National Stud in 2017, on days with many incoming customers, I had to direct cars to the three parking areas with no staff or security to aid me. Through careful placement of vehicles and knowledge of how much space was available, I was able to ensure that customers would be able to park and enter the tourist grounds. I was later informed that through my actions, I had helped the stud make a turnover larger than the season of 2016.

#### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

**RESULTS PENDING** 

# University name TBC/5/2018

Games and Apps Designer

Carlow PLC 12/11/2013

Graduated

Rathangan High School 12/12/2009

## **PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS**

None

## IT SKILLS & LANGUAGES

- · Include details of all IT skills and software knowledge you have to offer potential employers. Example: IT Skills: Wordpress, AutoCad, Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook and Explorer.
- List languages and competency level conversational, fluent, mother tongue etc.

## **INTERESTS**

I have interests in sculpting and modelling, having handmade miniatures using modelling clay and soft wax, and animation and the technical aspects behind it, such as rendering, resource management and movement.

I would like to combine my modelling hobby with 3D printing and scanning technology to put my creations into a 3D rendering and sculpting software tool to refine the detail on them.